storyfire.com 2019-05-21

# 

StoryFire, Inc. Privacy Policy

Effective Date:  March 28, 2017

Welcome to the website or App of StoryFire, Inc. (“StoryFire”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”). We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect and disclose information and data when you use any StoryFire website ("Site(s)") and any StoryFire services, including any company social networking accounts, company mobile applications (the "App(s)"), or other services offered by StoryFire from time to time and other services offered through third parties that integrate with StoryFire services or functionality (collectively, "Services"). "You" refers to you as a user of the Site or Services. 

BY USING THE SITE OR SERVICES YOU CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

Managing Your Information Preferences

You can opt out of receiving certain emails by changing notification settings on the Site or in our Apps, clicking the unsubscribe link provided in an email.  If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy [at] storyfire [dot] com. If and when we make accounts available via our App, you will able to review and update your Personal Information by changing the relevant settings in your StoryFire account. 

Information We Collect

Personal Information

We collect information that you provide directly to us (as opposed to information that you make publicly available that is described below) that personally identifies you, such as your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, payment, usage record and other personally identifiable information when you submit it via the Site ("Personal Information").  The decision to provide this information is optional.  However, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of the Site or Services.

Our App may collect certain additional information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device’s unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the App. We may also use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location. If you do not want us to have your location information, you should turn off the location services for the App located in your account settings or in your mobile phone settings and/or within the App. 

Usage Data and Site Activity

We automatically collect information regarding the actions you take on the Site and Services ("Usage Data").  Usage Data is information or content we collect about the use of our Site or Services in a way that does not identify an individual user. Usage Data helps us understand trends in our users’ needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor or enhance our Services. This Privacy Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of Usage Data, and we may share Usage Data about our users with third parties for various purposes, including to help us better understand our customers’ needs and improve our Services. For example, each time you use the Services we may automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the pages you view, how you interact with the Services, comments and other content made available via the Services and the time and duration of your visits to the Site or use of the Services.  This Usage Data may be associated with your account, but we do not disclose your Personal Information to third parties unless otherwise provided herein.  We may store such Usage Data itself and/or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by StoryFire affiliates, agents or service providers. We may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, the number of App downloads, the content viewed within the Services, etc.

Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser).  We may also use Web beacons (a file placed on a website that monitors usage).  We will use cookies and Web beacons to improve the experience of the Site and Services, such as pre-populating your username for easier login.  We do not use cookies or Web beacons to collect Personal Information.  Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies.  At this time, StoryFire does not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking, including “do-not-track” signals. You can remove persistent cookies and change your privacy preferences by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory.  However, certain features of the Site or Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies.  Some of our Service Providers may use their own cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf, as further explained below. 

Analytics

We may use third party analytics services such as Google Analytics Advertising Features, including: Remarketing with Google Analytics and Google Analytics Demographic and Interest Reporting. For information about Google Analytics’ currently available opt-outs, please click[ ](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/&sa=D&ust=1491510614219000&usg=AFQjCNH7VCrgzDyH_R5qaYCvRqxafZ5EnQ)[here](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/&sa=D&ust=1491510614219000&usg=AFQjCNH7VCrgzDyH_R5qaYCvRqxafZ5EnQ). You can also opt out of the above Google Analytics Advertising Features or adjust your settings via Google’s “Ads Settings” feature and you can generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the[ ](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp&sa=D&ust=1491510614220000&usg=AFQjCNF-h05sPUYhThFmV_13wGyjp1DuLw)[Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp&sa=D&ust=1491510614221000&usg=AFQjCNGP7uDoJ4-zbXZCK5rZQKDsciF6aA) or who follow the[ ](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.aboutads.info/choices/&sa=D&ust=1491510614222000&usg=AFQjCNFKIUi25IQ8gFYkV_T5iR7DRxnNYA)[Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.aboutads.info/choices/&sa=D&ust=1491510614222000&usg=AFQjCNFKIUi25IQ8gFYkV_T5iR7DRxnNYA) by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI site and DAA site.

How We Use Information and When We May Share and Disclose Information Generally

We may use your Personal Information for the purpose for which it was provided, including without limitation for the purposes described further below:

•               Provision and Monitoring of the Services:  We will use your Personal Information to provide you with access to and to support your use of the Services and to monitor your use of the Services.

•               Surveys, Contests and Other Special Offers: From time to time, we may offer our users the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests and other special offers.  If you elect to participate in these services, you may need to provide certain Personal Information.

•               Questions and Requests: If you contact us by e-mail or otherwise, we will use the Personal Information you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem.

•               Contacting You About Other Products, Services and Events:  If you opt-in, StoryFire and/or third parties may use your Personal Information to contact you in the future to tell you about products, services and events that may be of interest to you.

•               Research and Data Analysis: In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Site and the Services, StoryFire may conduct research on its customers’ demographics, interests and behavior based on Usage Data and other information provided to us. This data may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and StoryFire may share this data with advertisers, researchers, business partners, publications, and other third parties. This information will not identify you personally.

•               Service Improvement: We may use your Personal Information, aggregated Personal Information and other non-personally-identifiable information collected through the Site and Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Site, to better understand our users and to improve the Services.

Information You Make Publicly Available

By using the Site or Services, including submission of public content (e.g. photos or videos) or queries, you may choose to make certain of your Personal Information available to others, such as your name and your likeness.  Please be aware that any information you make publicly available may be accessed by anyone, including users who use the Site or Services and commercial search engines such as Google, Yahoo!, and Bing to the extent that such engines are permitted to access the Site or Services.

Third Party Services and Applications

Through the Site or Services, you may elect to access third-party services and applications, such as Instagram, Snapchat, Facebook and other social networks. When you do so, you may be able to import information from those other services and applications and share content with those services.  Some of those third-party services may also provide us with information from your accounts, which may enable us to enhance and personalize your use of the Site and Services.  If you elect to enable such third-party services or applications, the information you share with such third-party services and applications will be subject to their privacy policies and your privacy settings.  You may be able to control or block such sharing by changing your privacy settings in such services or applications. Please note that we do not authorize third parties to collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use the Site or Services. 

Service Providers

From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses that we believe to be trustworthy and have privacy practices consistent with ours ("Service Providers").  For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting and maintenance, data storage and management, and marketing and promotions.  We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf.  Each Service Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.  Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified by StoryFire. 

Advertising

We may work with third-party advertisers, search providers, and ad networks ("Advertisers").  These companies may collect and use information about your use of the Site or Services in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  Advertisements may be shown via the Site, the Services, or third-party websites and online services.  These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons.  Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that Advertisers may collect from you or that you choose to provide to them.

Other Transfers

We may share Personal Information and Usage Data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with StoryFire.  If StoryFire is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets or equity, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Usage Data in connection with such transaction. 

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

StoryFire will cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law.  We may disclose Personal Information and any other content and information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of StoryFire or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

Exclusions

This Privacy Policy will not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to StoryFire through the Site or Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as bulletin boards, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and StoryFire shall be free, and you hereby grant StoryFire, the perpetual, royalty-free right, to reproduce, disclose, distribute and otherwise use such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

Security

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of Personal Information and other information transmitted to us.  However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Site or Services, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site or Services, and you do so at your own risk.

Links

Our Site and Services may contain links or integrate with other websites and online services, or allow others to send you such links.  StoryFire is not responsible or liable for any damage or loss related to your use of any third-party website or online service.  You should always read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of a third-party website or online service before using it, whether directly or in connection with your use of the Site or Services.

Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13.  If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

Processing in the United States 

Please be aware that your Personal Information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, or country. Specifically, by using our Site or Services, you agree that you are transferring your Personal Information to the United States. You agree that the applicable laws in the United States will govern the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Personal Information and communications. The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location.

Privacy Policy Changes

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy.  If we change this Privacy Policy, we will give you notice by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site.  Those changes will go into effect on the effective date shown in the revised Privacy Policy.  By continuing to use the Site or Services, you consent to the revised Privacy Policy. 

PLEASE PRINT A COPY OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOR YOU RECORDS AND PLEASE CHECK THE SITE FREQUENTLY FOR ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
